import React from "react";

// TO DO: Add Images after every question is answered.
// TO DO: Add confetti animations at the end

const quizData = [
  {
    question: "What color is Mars often called?",
    a: "Blue Planet",
    b: "Red Planet",
    c: "Yellow Planet",
    d: "Green Planet",
    correct: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Mars is the ___ planet from the Sun.",
    a: "Second",
    b: "Third",
    c: "Fourth",
    d: "Fifth",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Which planet is right next to Mars in the solar system?",
    a: "Jupiter",
    b: "Earth",
    c: "Venus",
    d: "Saturn",
    correct: "b",
  },

  /*
A) Mount Mars
B) Olympus Mons
C) Mars Peak
D) Red Hill
*/
  {
    question: "What is the name of the largest volcano on Mars?",
    a: "Mount Mars",
    b: "Olympus Mons",
    c: "Mars Peak",
    d: "Red Hill",
    correct: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: Humans have landed on Mars.",
    a: "True",
    b: "False",
    correct: "False",
  },

  /*
  
What is the weather like on Mars?
A) Very hot all year
B) Super rainy
C) Cold and dusty
D) Like Hawaii
✅ Answer: C) Cold and dusty

What does Mars have that looks a lot like Earth’s features?
A) Oceans
B) Shopping malls
C) Mountains and valleys
D) Forests
✅ Answer: C) Mountains and valleys
  */
  {
    question: "What is a “rover” on Mars??",
    a: "A type of spaceship",
    b: "A Mars dog",
    c: "A robot that explores the planet",
    d: "A kind of alien",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Mars has how many moons?",
    a: "0",
    b: "1",
    c: "5",
    d: "2",
    correct: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Which U.S. space agency sends rovers to Mars?",
    a: "NASA",
    b: "SpaceX",
    c: "Blue Origin",
    d: "Tesla",
    correct: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the weather like on Mars?",
    a: "Very hot all year",
    b: "Super rainy",
    c: "Cold and dusty",
    d: "Like Hawaii",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Mars have that looks a lot like Earth’s features?",
    a: "Oceans",
    b: "Shopping malls",
    c: "Mountains and valleys",
    d: "Forests",
    correct: "c",
  },
];

export default quizData;
